Amos Hason

■ amos@hason.science

⊘ amos.hason.science

in amos-hason

• AmosHason

About Me

Independent and self-disciplined autodidact with proven self-learning abilities. Curious, ambitious, and passionate about artificial intelligence research and development. Able to quickly adapt to new development environments, platforms, technologies, and methodologies.

Available for full-time onsite and remote work. Able to relocate.

Education

Ben-Gurion University of the Negev

Mar 2022 - Dec 2024

M.Sc. in Computer Science

- Focus: Intelligent and Autonomous Systems
- Research Area: Unsupervised Sequential Disentangled Representation Learning
- Skills: Deep Learning, Deep Generative Models, Time Series Models, Signal Processing, Computer Vision, Music Information Retrieval
- **Teaching:** Algorithms, Python
- **GPA:** 90/100

The Open University of Israel

Mar 2015 - May 2017

B.Sc. in Sciences: Emphasis on Computer Science

- Skills: Artificial Intelligence, Computational Intelligence, Computational Creativity, Data Mining, Machine Learning, Artificial
 Neural Networks, Evolutionary Computation, Algorithms, System Programming, Object-Oriented Programming, Functional
 Programming, Programming Language Theory, Database Systems, Physics, Chemistry, Meteorology
- **GPA:** 88/100 (Honors Graduate), Top 20%

Professional Experience

Software Engineer

Herzliya, Israel

Varonis

Oct 2020 - June 2021

• Backend software design and development using C# (.NET Framework) and Python in a team that productizes a data security insight generation feature that is based on user profiling and peering.

Software Engineer

Tel Aviv, Israel Feb 2018 – Oct 2020

Fabric

• Software design and development in a multi-disciplinary robotics environment using C# (.NET Core) and Python.

- Initiating software projects from scratch as well as developing existing software projects.
- Involvement in the entire software life cycle: planning, prioritizing, design, development, testing, integration, and release.

QA Engineer

Tel Aviv, Israel

Check Point Software Technologies

Mar 2013 - Nov 2014

• Performance testing of network security solutions.

Technologies

Programming Languages: Python, C#, Java, C, Lisp, F#

Libraries: PyTorch, PyTorch Lightning, NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib

HPC: Slurm

MLOps: Neptune

Typesetting: LaTeX